<odoo>
    <data>

        <template id="aboutuscustom" inherit_id="website.aboutus">
             <xpath expr="//h3[@class='text-muted text-center']" position="replace">
                <h3 class="text-muted text-center">"To Think only the best, To Work only for the best and To Expect for the best"</h3>
             </xpath>
            <xpath expr="//div[@class='col-md-6 mt32']" position="replace">
                <div class="col-md-6 mt32">
                    <img src="/etsi_base/static/src/img/wsi_about_us.jpg" class="img img-responsive shadow" alt="Our Team"/>
                    <br/>
                    <h5 style="font-weight:bold;">Who we are?</h5>
                    <p align="justify">Organizations, like individuals, are often judged by the company they keep. Here at WeSupport,
                        we firmly believe that organizations of integrity and substance should seek to align themselves
                        with other organizations that share the same values and commitments. In today’s environment of corporate
                        uncertainty, coupled with an ever increasing demand for ethical accountability, WeSupport Incorporated
                        is an ideal partner for business industry in the Philippines.
                    </p>

                    <h5 style="font-weight:bold;">History</h5>
                    <p align="justify">WeSupport Inc. (WSI) is a Filipino-owned company established in 2006. Initially, the company ventured to staff
                        augmentation and general services only. Throughout the years, WSI continues to excel in the providing the best
                        human resource which focuses on IT professional contracts provider, managed services and staff augmentation to different industries.
                        Today, WeSupport is the premier provider of IT services in the country’s top telecommunications company.
                    </p>
                    <div class="col-md-6 mt32">
                        <h5 style="font-weight:bold">Our Mission</h5>
                        <p align="justify">To support and promote the Philippine business community in achieving world-class IT related services through multi-skilled,
                            well-trained, and very disciplined people.
                        </p>
                    </div>
                     <div class="col-md-6 mt32">
                        <h5 style="font-weight:bold">Our Vision</h5>
                        <p align="justify">Relying on a strong local foundation, WeSupport, Incorporated envisions to being the major player in providing IT Support Services.
                        </p>
                    </div>


                </div>

             </xpath>

        </template>

    </data>
</odoo>